politicaldig.com 2019-09-26

# Privacy - Political Dig

Welcome to our website. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy, which applies to this website or our mobile applications (for example our iPhone and iPad apps) (a “Site”). If you do not accept these this privacy policy, do not use this Site.

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) when you complete registration or inquiry forms, submit comments to the Site, participate in message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities or send emails to us. By submitting information to our website we have full legal permission to use all information for our editorial purposes. Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

COLLECTION OF OTHER INFORMATION/COOKIES  
In addition to personal information, we may collect information about you automatically when you visit the Site. The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor traffic on the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser when you first visit the Site. The cookie allows us to identify your computer and find out details about your last visit. Most Internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. Generally you have the option to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is issued or reject all cookies. Click here, for instructions on controlling cookies in the most recent version of Windows Explorer (Users of other browsers should contact their manufacturer for instructions). If you choose not to receive our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience with the Site will be as quick or responsive as if you do receive cookies. The information collected by cookies and web beacons is not personally identifiable, it includes general information about your computer settings, your connection to the Internet e.g. operating system and platform, IP address, your browsing patterns and timings of browsing on the Site and geographical location.

INTEREST BASED ADVERTISING   
Interest based advertisements on our site are provided by our advertising partner. Our advertising partner will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on certain information about your visit to this and other websites. This information is collected and used without reference to other data which could identify you in the real world, in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number. In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. You have the right to exercise control over the way we collect and use information about your online activities in this way and you are entitled to opt-out of receiving this type of interest based advertising. Please note that the effectiveness of any opt-out for interest based advertising may be impacted by deleting all cookies on your browser. You can also refer to the privacy policy of our advertising partner for further information on interest based advertising on other sites served by their system.

USE OF YOUR INFORMATION  
By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business which shall include (without limitation):  
1\. Verifying your identity (for example when you return to the Site)  
2\. Personalizing your visits to the Site and developing the design and style of the Site to improve the services provided to you  
3\. Informing you about the latest changes to the Site, or products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting  
4\. Dealing with, and responding to you about, a comment you have submitted for or on our message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities  
5\. Enabling you to share our content with others e.g. using our Email a friend and Share this article facilities  
6\. Communicating (and personalizing such communication) with you  
7\. Informing you if you have been successful in any Site competitions or promotions  
8\. Compiling customer reviews  
9\. Conducting market research  
10\. Carrying out statistical, technical and logistical analysis

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
By using the Site, you agree that we may disclose your personal information to any company within our group of companies. Subject to obtaining your consent, we may also supply personal information about you to third parties.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to comply with applicable laws (such as the Data Protection Act 1998) and government or regulatory bodies’ lawful requests for information. Additionally, we may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganization of our business.  
Message Boards, Blogs and Other Public Forums

The Site makes message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities available to users of the Site and registered users can provide content for and participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas of our Site becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Email A Friend and Share This Article Facilities:  
When you use these facilities and provide us with personal data (e.g. the name and email address) of a third party, please ensure that you have their consent before giving us their details.
